<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FOSS Grid</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FOSS Grid</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LibreOffice 7.0.4 Released</title>
      <link>/news/libreoffice-7.0.4-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/libreoffice-7.0.4-released/</guid>
      <description>The document foundation released LibreOffice 7.0.4 on December 17, 2020. Visit https://blog.documentfoundation.org/blog/2020/12/17/libreoffice-704/ for the official release announcment.
LibreOffice is a free and open-source office suite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GTK 4.0 Released</title>
      <link>/news/gtk-4.0-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/gtk-4.0-released/</guid>
      <description>The GTK Development Blog announced the the release of GTK 4.0:
 2020 has been a very long year. What better way to end it than with a major release! Today, we released GTK 4.0.
 GTK 4.0 comes with many new features that include an advanced data transfer framework, layout managers and transforms, shaders, etc.
On the support of older versions of GTK, the announcement mentioned that GTK 2 has reached the end of life and GTK 3 will continue to be supported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bash 5.1 Released</title>
      <link>/news/bash-5.1-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/bash-5.1-released/</guid>
      <description>The GNU project has released Bash 5.1. Chet Ramey posted an email to the info-gnu mailing list and announced:
 This is the fifth major release of bash. Read the file NEWS in the bash-5.1 distribution for a complete description of the new features.
 The announcement further describes the following new features:
 This release fixes several outstanding bugs in bash-5.0 and introduces several new features. The most significant change is a return to the bash-4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About FOSS Grid</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>FOSS Grid brings to you the latest news and updates in free and open source software.
If you have a tip or news item you would like to see on FOSS Grid, please send your tip or news item to in simple text or Markdown format to the following email address: fossgrid@outlook.com.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
